Not at the table, son.
Come on.
Mmm-mmm.
Grace first.
You know better.
Father, we are gathered here
to share this food in your name.
Bless this food into our bodies, O Lord.
Bless our hearts
and all that we do, O Lord,
so that we may walk in your name...
Who will that be at this time?
I have no idea.
No.
♫  Three and thirty years  ♫
♫  I tried  ♫
♫  To forget  ♫
♫  All the tears I cried  ♫
Leave my family alone.
Theodore.
It's okay.
♫  Then one who knew me long ago...  ♫
Leave them out of this.
Your quarrel is with me.
Let's go outside, take a walk,
and handle our business.
- Please.
- No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please, I'm begging you.
No!
No! No! No! No!
No! No! No!
No! No! Please!
No!
No! No, no, no, no, no! No!
Father Esparza?
I'm here for confession...
and the collection.
You know what happens
when you're late with my coins.
What possesses a man
to paint a scorpion on his hand?
Excuse me?
A snake,
I understand that.
The Garden of Eden, the Bible, etcetera.
But a scorpion?
Well, that puzzles me.
Who are you?
Just a man.
Here to kill the Scorpion.
Jesus Cortez.
Those were, uh, different times.
Whatever happened between you and I
must have been a long, long time ago.
No.
Please.
I...
I'm sorry.
Colored Italics & Music by Sailor420
!!! Hope you enjoy the show !!!
Is it over?
This is a wanted man.
Turn his body in,
you'll get $5,000 for your church.
Why aren't you
taking him in yourself?
I'm worth ten.
♫  Avalon be damned  ♫
♫  Venture foreign lands  ♫
♫  I laid my sword in the sand  ♫
♫  I've made my peace with man  ♫
♫  They lay a violent feast  ♫
♫  As far as my eyes can see  ♫
♫  I seek a golden fleece  ♫
♫  One day you'll make your peace  ♫
♫  So don't tempt my hand  ♫
♫  I'm just a man  ♫
♫  A deadly scene, a weathered being  ♫
♫  Men must cry where soldiers lie  ♫
♫  On threatened land
My guns go bang  ♫
♫  I can make the guns go bang  ♫
♫  I make all the guns go bang  ♫
♫  Dot Seventeen with the switch
It'll change you  ♫
♫  Mama always said you was an angel  ♫
♫  Papa got ghost
But these doors he never came through  ♫
♫  He got ghost
But those walls he never came through  ♫
♫  Stain glass windows in the church
I hope you stain proof  ♫
♫  'Cause when the tides change
I'm tryna stain you  ♫
♫  Plotting for revenge
Dig your grave too  ♫
♫  Whatever you want engraved
What your tombstone will say too  ♫
♫  Crosses on the head of an angel  ♫
♫  Sins of the father darken the doorstep
I became you  ♫
♫  Faithful till the end  ♫
♫  Bullets with your names drew
Cock back, aim, shoot, bang  ♫
♫  Fragile life
A reflection of the past we leave behind  ♫
♫  For sake of something new  ♫
♫  Fractured smile, open windows
To the wounds we try to hide  ♫
♫  Engraved in shadowed rooms  ♫
♫  Bird in flight  ♫
Yeah!
♫  Upon my return  ♫
♫  See a changed soul  ♫
♫  That road was far  ♫
♫  And way too long  ♫
♫  They'll run from me  ♫
♫  As they ran from you  ♫
♫  That fear in me  ♫
♫  Is in a distant...  ♫
♫  View  ♫
It's the Nat Love Gang!
Stop firing! Stop firing!
It's one man! We got him pinned!
Wait for his head to show,
then blow the naps off that motherfucker.
Be patient.
I hear patience is a virtue.
But I ain't never been able to wait
to see if the motherfucker true.
- Jim Beckwourth.
- Brothers Grime.
It's Grimes with an "S,"
you egotistical piece of shit.
I remember a time
y'all hoods used to be crimson.
Known as the Crimson Hood Gang.
Them motherfuckers pink now.
You know, Mama used to say, "Jim is
such a sweet boy." You know what I said?
"Mama, fuck Jim!
Look what he did to my fucking eye!"
- I am sweet.
- You're not sweet.
- I'm sweet.
- You're not.
- Bitch, I'm sweet.
- You know what?
I'd rather be dead
than hear this motherfucker keep talking.
Whoo.
Much obliged, motherfuckers.
What the hell is that shit,
playing quick-draw games
when my ass is getting shot at?
Hey, hey.
You got your lucky coin, don't you?
Grow up, Jim.
This is real grown-men shit. We can die.
But we not gonna die.
'Cause I'm lightnin'
with the blam-blams. Admit it.
You know, you might could be,
but I hearsay there's a quick draw
more lightnin' than you,
go by the name of Cherokee Bill.
"Cherokee Bill."
You hearsay.
You don't see-say.
So I say fuck Cherokee Bill.
You know, rather than complaining,
you should be applauding my performance.
The only words that should be
coming out your Black-ass lips...
- "Black-ass lips"?
- ...should be...
- ...gracias.
- That was smooth.
- I know.
- Black lips are beautiful lips.
- Would you stop reaching, negro?
- God damn.
You just killed my brother.
Your half-brother, calm down.
Look like your day going a little bad.
Better than you sons of bitches
when you find out
whose money you done fucked with.
Correction. Who you done fucked with.
Y'all rob banks. We rob y'all.
And ain't a negro from here to Africa
gonna know we even exist.
You think I'm talking about a bank?
♫  I don't know  ♫
♫  Where they go-oh-oh-oh-oh  ♫
♫  Where are the children of men?  ♫
♫  Questions that we did not know  ♫
♫  Did not know  ♫
♫  When will we see them again?  ♫
♫  Questions that we did not know  ♫
♫  Did not know  ♫
♫  For queens and kings
And shining things  ♫
♫  They gave our souls  ♫
♫  But they soon learned
That freedom's better than gold  ♫
♫  Oh, inna the days of old  ♫
♫  Inna the days of old  ♫
♫  These are the tales untold  ♫
Evening, gent. Kindly check your weapon
and enjoy the festivities.
This is Stagecoach Mary's place
and ain't no guns allowed?
'Cept for Mary's, naturally.
Naturally.
Naturally, she put a fresh-faced pup
like yourself here to see to it.
Oh, I got to see
to a lot of things, Mr. Love.
People see me and they don't feel
too intimidated by what they see. See?
We familiar?
No, but you right famous
around these parts.
Folks say you once cut down
three men with one bullet.
Now, I ain't met a man
who can do that yet. Excuse me.
Evening, gents. Kindly check your weapons
and enjoy your evening.
I'd sooner check my right arm, boy.
Then you can head on over
to Jourdon Anderson's.
You can hold your weapon
and drink over there.
We drinking here, you puny little fuck.
Hey!
Some folk tend to feel a way, regardless.
Get 'em over to Doc Brown's.
Take they guns to the sheriff.
They can get 'em back
when they leave town.
What they call you?
They call me Cuffee.
This why I'm here!
Don't hurt nobody!
♫  One!
Get that horse and his wagon  ♫
♫  Two!
Get that man and his rifle  ♫
♫  Three!
Get that priest and his Bible  ♫
♫  Four!
For them that's dead on arrival  ♫
♫  Five!
Them that pray see heaven  ♫
♫  Six!
Them that don't see the devil  ♫
♫  Seven!
Separate but equal  ♫
♫  Eight!
Say them that slaved my people  ♫
♫  Nine!
So break them chains and shackles  ♫
♫  Ten!  ♫
Come again.
♫  One!
Get that horse and its wagon  ♫
♫  Two!
Get that man and his rifle  ♫
♫  Three!
Get that priest and his Bible  ♫
♫  Four!
For them that's dead on arrival  ♫
♫  Five!
Them that pray see heaven  ♫
♫  Six!
Them that don't see the devil  ♫
♫  Seven!
Separate but equal  ♫
♫  Eight!
Say them that slaved my people  ♫
♫  Nine!
So break them chains and shackles  ♫
♫  Ten!  ♫
Not again.
You still ain't talking to me?
Get out.
What?
I said leave.
What was that kiss for, then?
To remind you of what it was.
That's to remind you of what it is.
Excuse me.
Cuff, clean this man up.
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Second floor. Third room on the left.
Mary.
The only thing I need to hear
coming out your mouth is "Goodbye, Mary."
The one thing
you'll never hear me say again.
Till the next time you hear tell
of the whereabouts
of some man that done you dirt.
Ain't none of them left.
So you found the Scorpion?
Mary, the only thing that mean anything
to me in this world now
is you.
And what about the Nat Love Gang?
Ain't been much of a gang since you left.
Just me, Jim, Bill.
Next time they come around, I'll sort it.
Mmm.
You know, I can almost believe that.
Almost, 'cause you didn't get
the last one, did you?
You can say his name, Mary.
What about Rufus Buck?
Rufus in Yuma
for the rest of his natural life.
For a man like him,
that's worse than death.
As long as that man draw breath,
your spirit is gonna be cursed
and wild as it ever was.
Hmm.
I made things,
I built things,
and I ain't gonna risk all that
just because you decide
to come trottin' back.
- "Trottin'"?
- Yeah.
- Okay, well.
- Mmm-hmm.
I guess I came to the wrong saloon
'cause I ain't talking
to the Mary Fields I thought I knew.
- Yep. Things have changed.
- I see that.
Mmm-hmm.
'Cause that Mary...
That Mary...
...don't shy away from nothin'.
What was it the Apache called you?
Wolf Lady?
No. That's some bullshit
Pickett used to say.
That's bullshit Pickett used to say.
- Apache called me Coyote Woman.
- Hmm.
Yeah, Wolf Lady more like it.
My hat.
There.
I'm coming in.
Now, Wolf Lady,
don't blow the head off my neck.
- Nat.
- Pickett.
You got the worst timing
in the history of timing.
Oh, y'all was makin' sex?
I apologize.
But what I got to show you can't wait.
Well, well, well.
If it ain't the debonair dipshit himself.
Whoa, easy, Nat.
Listen to what the man got to say first.
So he can tell me
the same stories he been tellin' you?
Why the fuck would I lie?
Rufus Buck is behind bars
for the rest of his life.
- He gettin' out.
- How?
Damned if I know.
I just know it's so.
All the gangs are gettin' set
to ride for him again.
Half that take was his.
And you fools took his money.
You think Rufus Buck
was gonna let you keep half that money,
and you callin' me a fool?
I guess I am.
On your feet.
Exhale.
Now get out of here.
Leave.
What you doin'? We coulda killed
the last of the Crimson Hoods.
It's called the Crimson Hood Gang.
You think that's the last one?
Yeah.
I woulda bet my left six-shooter
he was about to kill that boy.
If that man telling the truth,
Nat just did him a whole lot worse.
♫  Whoa, seen! Here I come!  ♫
♫  Here I come!  ♫
What the hell
are you doin' out here?
That ain't no way to board a train,
you damn stupid ni...
You know, he might coulda said nincompoop.
We ain't no nincompoop.
If they say something
that even start with "N,"
they gonna meet the same fate.
Let 'em see your faces.
All right, stay calm, everybody.
Don't... Hey, don't touch nothin'.
My name is Cherokee Bill.
Now let it be known
that I don't particularly enjoy violence.
That being said,
you are currently in the company
of extremely violent individuals.
Try some of that.
Ugh. Shit.
So, don't do no stupid shit. All right?
Get off this train now,
you motherless scum.
You must be the hero.
Great Spirit, why is there always one?
You're rude.
I might actually enjoy
inflicting violence on you.
But who knows?
Maybe you'll win.
Let's see.
See my point?
Now, step aside so that we may conclude
our business here without further ado.
All right, everybody...
Stop right there.
No.
I said stop.
Put the weapon down, boy.
Or we kill everybody on this train.
I said put the gun down.
It's okay.
Are there any more soldiers on that car?
There are.
Exactly how many?
Thirty.
Ten!
See, that's all you had to say.
Open the door.
I said open the damn door.
Here we are.
My dear battalion.
I imagine you have
all your artillery aimed at the door.
I'd like to inform you
that in front of that door
lies one of your very own troops.
Any bullets coming through that door
will hit him first, okay?
State your name, criminal.
Oh, I'm not a criminal, sir, um,
but my name is Cherokee Bill.
What's your name?
My name is Officiant of the Goddamn Law.
You let that soldier go immediately.
Leave this train now
and no one will be hurt.
Oh, that sounds like fear talking,
Mr. Officiant of the Goddamn Law.
And we done already hurt a couple people.
You're just going to let us
get away Dred Scott free?
State your purpose, bastard.
Also, I'm not a bastard.
But you've got something we want.
We've got a soldier that you want.
Now, I suggest we make a peaceful trade
and everybody lives to see another day.
- Sound dandy?
- Just let the boy go.
Jake!
I'm okay, Pa!
That's just a flesh wound, sir.
You got ten seconds to put your guns down
and open up this damn door,
or your little kin here shall perish.
Harm him further and I will kill every
last one of you godless sons of bitches.
Goddamn, Trudy.
You know I like my countdowns.
My apologies, sir.
My friend here doesn't like arithmetic.
Be that as it may, seven seconds.
Six.
- Lay down your rifles.
- Five.
I said lay them down.
Four.
Three.
Well, all right. Thank you kindly.
Go ahead and walk, boy.
Keep walkin'. Just keep moving.
No one do anything stupid.
Just walk like you been taught.
Left, right, left. Left, right, left.
Left, right, left.
♫  Skip to the Lou, my darlin'  ♫
- Open it.
- I can't.
The key is back in Yuma. And the next...
One more time.
You will be hounded
to the ends of the earth for this.
I don't like long distances,
Lieutenant General Abbott.
Ever cross your mind
why you was given the task
of transporting a lone outlaw
from one prison to another?
Full pardon for Mr. Buck
and all his associates for all misdeeds.
Signed General George Pryce.
What's this about?
Well, he came to us with a proposition.
Kill a particular
Officiant of the Goddamn Law.
A man so crooked that even the government
is embarrassed by his misdeeds.
Apparently, you and your men
wiped out an entire town,
women and children included,
to steal silver.
- Now, that's some unscrupulous shit.
- Unscrupulous shit.
Please. I'll dis...
Shh.
No!
Pa! No, no, no, no, no.
Pa.
No.
Who here can drive a train?
I said...
Everybody but him.
♫  Whoa, seen! Here I come!  ♫
♫  I'm broad  ♫
♫  I'm broader than Broadway  ♫
Evening, sir. Check your weapon with me
and enjoy what's left of the night.
Oh, no need to show me that star.
I know who you is.
In here, though, I be the sheriff,
and that make Ms. Mary the marshal.
And the marshal say,
"Don't nobody come in here gunned up,
or they might could get gunned down."
My badge begs to differ.
Check your gun-belt.
Excuse me.
So how you plan on taking me in, Marshal?
Staring me to death?
How about just death?
Just a pipe.
You mind?
Never known you to touch it.
Only after I kill a man.
Or before.
I was on the trail
of the Crimson Hood Gang
on account of a bank robbery
in Kansas City.
Turned out somebody got to 'em before me.
You know I don't rob banks, Marshal.
But you rob them that do,
which is all the same to me.
- Texas.
- What?
I was in Texas
at the time of that robbery.
How you know when it took place?
Whenever any bank robbery took place,
I was in Texas.
Unless, of course,
the robbery took place in Texas.
Way I hear it, some of them boys
with the Crimson Hoods
are part of a new Rufus Buck Gang, Nat.
Rufus in Yuma.
He out. But you knew that already,
didn't you?
Why you sitting here monologuing,
drinking up my whiskey,
when you should be out
rounding up your little deputies?
'Cause he been pardoned, Nat.
Rufus Buck been absolved
of his countless depredations.
Seeing as I've been scouring the terrain
looking for bank robbers and such,
that particular piece of news
failed to reach me.
What they sayin'?
Something about guns, killin'.
Why you let that kid take my gun?
What kinda stupid rule is that?
- Should be four guns pointing at...
- Shut up, Pickett.
You shoot, he dead.
You miss,
all y'all die.
You, come here.
Take these cuffs. Cuff this man.
Or I put three in his chest right now,
lessen the trouble.
Go on.
Tell this young buck to back up.
Easy, Jim.
Everybody in here know who I am.
I'm taking Nat Love
to Fort Smith to be tried.
Anybody try to follow me,
y'all know what I do.
Come on.
Y'all enjoy the rest of the evening.
♫  Well, now  ♫
♫  Whoa-oh, well  ♫
♫  The promise land  ♫
♫  Going to the promise land  ♫
♫  Yes, the promise land  ♫
♫  Oh gosh now  ♫
♫  To the promise land  ♫
♫  Make a step down to Wasmara  ♫
♫  Then we stopped in Addis Ababa  ♫
♫  Made our way to Shashamane land  ♫
♫  Riding on the king's highway  ♫
♫  To the promise land  ♫
♫  Going to the promise land  ♫
♫  Oh gosh  ♫
♫  To the promise land  ♫
♫  Yeah, the promise land  ♫
Rufus.
Cherokee Bill, Ms. Smith,
top of the morning to you both.
Mr. Buck, glad to have you
back in Redwood, sir.
Any word on the take
from the Kansas City bank?
The Crimson Hoods took it for $25,000.
But they were ambushed
before they got here.
Everybody knows
it's suicide to take from us.
Someone obviously disagrees.
Goddamn it. That just put us
right back where we started.
How we supposed to build a Mecca
without any bricks?
We gonna have to
take it out of our own bank.
We don't have
that type of money, Trudy.
We only got a few pennies over $2,500.
What did he say?
- 2,500...
- I heard you.
- Wiley.
- Yeah.
Sure is hot, ain't it?
What's up, little man?
- You wanna see something?
- Yeah.
Watch this now.
Don't take your eyes off it.
Oh, it's still there!
Rufus Buck.
Look at you.
Relic of yesteryear with nothin'.
And you think you can roll into my town
and take what belong to me?
Who the fuck you think I am, huh?
Ain't nobody scared of you
and ain't nobody runnin'.
I'm a sinister motherfucker too.
One click of my finger and you disappear.
So I suggest you leave...
before I finish my steak.
And if you even think about sticking...
Come in.
What is it, Carson?
Sheriff, Mr. Buck wants
to see you out front.
Tell that man
I ain't got nothing to say to him.
It wasn't a request.
Wiley Escoe.
Rufus.
You wanna sell this town
while I rot in prison?
The world you knew is gone.
There's a flood comin'.
Do you think
you can hold onto this place when it hit?
At least I know enough
to get mine and get out.
Kill me...
and you'll have nothing.
You know, a man like you
will have us all subservient
till the end of our days
so's long as you can buy yourself a house,
a badge,
and them goddamn gold teeth.
You want to do this here?
There you go.
That's what you want, right?
That's what you came here for?
I won't disappoint you. Come on.
That's what you want. Want some more?
You want some more, right?
You want some more?
Come here, motherfucker.
Here you go.
Oh shit. I done hit gold.
Hey, boy. Come here.
Come, get that gold. Get that gold.
All right. Tell your mama
you rich now! Go ahead!
Now,
I ain't gonna kill you, Wiley.
You and I were friends once.
But know this.
Redwood will never be yours, never.
Never.
Matter of fact,
you ain't welcome here no more.
Now...
I want you to vacate immediately
or die where you lay.
Say what?
That's right.
♫  Going home to my Lord  ♫
♫  I'm going home  ♫
♫  I'm going home now to my Lord  ♫
♫  I'm going home to my Lord  ♫
♫  I'm going home to my Lord  ♫
♫  I'm going home now to my Lord  ♫
You coulda taken these off a while back.
Yep.
Tell me something.
How you know Rufus will be in Redwood?
He's taking that money
from them Crimson Hoods.
That's where he'll be.
Now you teaming up
with a marshal to bring him in.
I ain't bringing him in.
I'm bringing him down.
And we ain't teaming up, old man.
Your life's expendable, Marshal.
My gang's ain't.
Shit, since we're out here,
I oughta tell you...
I was fixin' to kill you...
when you and your fellas brought in Rufus.
A lot of men be fixin', son.
They always seem to die
before they get the job done.
Just for the record...
I took Rufus in alone.
Mary.
I figured you'd be halfway
to Fort Smith by now.
You can put that gun down, Marshal.
This ain't a ambush.
You, on the other hand,
might wanna keep yours handy.
Do you think I'm stupid enough
to fall for that bullshit
y'all pulled in my saloon?
I don't want you mixed up in this no more.
Then you shoulda told me so.
I must confess
to some raw feelings myself.
This ain't no road
to ask a friend to travel.
Now you take that money
we took off them Crimson Hoods
and you buy that ranch
you always blabbing about. Hmm?
That's mighty generous of you,
but that ain't how this gang work.
Take stays in the usual place, ready
to be shared three ways when we come back.
Ain't no coming back from this.
Now get out of here.
All of you. This ain't your fight.
You take on the Devil himself, you gonna
need more than you and the marshal.
I seen the Devil,
and Rufus Buck ain't him.
Devil's white.
You got a reason you wanna die, Jim?
Outside of you saving me from this?
Besides, Monroe said
Cherokee Bill run with Rufus.
Every time I speak on my speed,
a motherfucker wanna pull
Cherokee Bill out they ass.
I'ma put a end to that argument
once and for all.
Like they say in the Book of Clarence,
"No man out-speed me."
Out-speed ain't a word,
and Clarence ain't no book.
I'm hopin' Cherokee put a bullet
in your ass just to shut you up.
- Hey.
- You left these on my wall, Mr. Love.
Figured we going after villains,
you'll need 'em.
Obliged.
What y'all waiting around for?
You think destiny is comin' to you?
Hyup! Go!
Yeah. I know.
Go ahead.
♫  Wahala they go
Wahala they come  ♫
♫  Wahala they ride
Wahala they run  ♫
♫  Wahala they sing  ♫
♫  Wahala they go
Wahala they come  ♫
♫  Wahala they ride
Wahala they run  ♫
♫  Wahala they sing
Wahala they call  ♫
♫  Wahala they fly
Wahala they fall  ♫
♫  Wahala they go
Wahala they come  ♫
♫  Wahala they ride
Wahala they run  ♫
How do I look?
All right.
Everybody out there?
Just about.
How could you do it?
Leave all of this to Wiley?
If you were runnin' Redwood,
who woulda kept the operation goin'?
Who else woulda kept
all them gangs in line?
Look, I know that Wiley got his ways,
but he was loyal once.
Loyalty is a virtue, Rufus.
Till it ain't.
You loyal to me?
See these folk here?
Either they can't see it
or they don't want to.
But I believe in what you're doing.
This place can be
the promised land for us.
And as long as that so, ain't nothing
I won't do to see it through.
You tell them.
Citizens of Redwood.
A new day is dawning.
As by now you have doubtless learned,
the territory will officially
open up for settlement.
Now they say everything we own
is gonna stay our own.
But you know as well as I do
how much that's worth.
See, your land,
your businesses, your homes
has all been promised
to the highest bidders
by your one-time sheriff, Wiley Escoe.
Now, Mr. Buck can prevent this
from happening.
But in order for us to do that,
it's necessary that we levy a tax.
At what cost to us?
- $50,000.
- Ooh.
You could scrape every penny
from every living soul in this town,
and it wouldn't come near to that.
You got us between a rock
and a hard place.
How long you been alive in this country?
A rock and a hard place
is what we call Monday.
I've heard of Rufus Buck.
How bad a man he is.
But he got himself
thrown in jail once before,
and I reckon
he'll be back there again soon enough.
When he is,
maybe I'll come back to this town.
'Cause I ain't paying shit.
You think I made Redwood for myself?
To what end?
Redwood ain't a hiding place,
'cause I don't hide.
It ain't a dream.
I don't dream.
You know what it is?
It's an example.
It's an example...
for others to follow.
And you...
you are an enemy of progress.
Please. Please.
- I got a family.
- What's your name?
James.
Rest in peace, James.
Now, how much?
How much can be gathered?
Ten thousand.
Maybe 15,
if every last cent can be squeezed.
Mmm-hmm.
Ain't nobody leave town
until we collect it all.
And if you fail to comply,
you and everything you love will burn.
I ain't got nothin' to rob.
But I got somebody to shoot.
Step down.
Wiley Escoe.
Bass Reeves.
Fuck.
Redwood crawling with gunmen.
Rufus came with 12 and took six of mine.
Who knows how many he got by now.
I don't believe a thing this man sayin'.
He a scout.
I say we kill him.
And we take the rest of them teeth.
You ever shot a sheriff, boy?
A mayor?
Little harder than shootin' regular folk.
And I'm both.
You both alive and dead
'cause Rufus don't like loose ends.
Law don't find a man like Rufus Buck
unless you got inside information.
Ain't that right, Wiley?
If I had my way, you'd be right up
under the jail next to Rufus.
But you cut yourself a deal,
wound up wearing a badge instead.
You got your reasons
you want Rufus gone, and I got mine.
Ain't the enemy of my enemy my friend?
Rufus tryin' to save Redwood.
But for that, he need money.
And that's one thing he ain't have.
All right, look here.
You made a deal with the Devil.
Now he come to collect.
You rest up,
but be gone before sunup.
Or it's gonna go from bad to badder.
You hear?
Ooh.
Marshal.
Marshal. Marshal.
All them tricks'll get you killed, son.
Listen, Marshal.
I'm faster than any weapon.
You can trust in that.
I seen faster.
All right. Where?
In the mirror.
Negro said, "In the mirror."
I'm so... I'm sorry.
I rather ride into a gun battle
on a dark horse over a golden stallion.
- Fuck that mean?
- Shiny shit get shot.
You gonna shoot me?
What you think about that, lawman?
I think y'all gonna die.
♫  And away with the wind  ♫
♫  She goes  ♫
♫  As her garden grows  ♫
♫  Hold those flowers close  ♫
♫  For away with the wind  ♫
♫  She goes  ♫
I'll be back with information by sunup.
Information from where?
Redwood.
You know we can't trust Wiley's word.
Someone's got to get the lay of the land
before we make our next move.
Yeah, Mary, but that somebody
ain't got to be you.
Every gunhand
in the territory's gonna recognize you
the second you hop off your horse.
Same with Bill and Beckwourth.
In case you forgot,
your face more famous than all of ours
put together, Stagecoach Mary.
Got it up on advertisements
for that saloon of yours
from here to Texas.
Which is why I can
ride into town in plain sight.
Everybody knows I'm buying saloons.
Rufus need money. I'ma make him an offer
on Trudy Smith's place...
Mary, what in my character
makes you think I'll allow that?
I'm not asking for your permission.
All right.
Then I... I guess
I'll just be asking you for yours.
Since you'll never let
a man give you away,
I just have to ask you direct.
That's the ring my father gave my mother.
I was gonna give it to you
back in Douglas.
But you didn't.
I am now.
I used to hate feeling helpless over you.
Those days are over now.
Mary...
When the dust settles,
we gonna go our separate ways, for good.
But not till the dust settles.
I'm here till then.
See you sunup.
♫  Woman cry, give life  ♫
♫  Mother Mary and baby
The burden she carries all time  ♫
♫  Woman cry gives us life  ♫
♫  And she begs he forgives us
The sin and the sinners all time  ♫
Whoa.
Are you a resident of Redwood, ma'am?
You don't own a gun
confident enough to ask where I reside.
Well, this gun say
answer the damn question.
Well, this gun don't talk.
Stagecoach Mary.
Ghastly Gertrude Smith.
I prefer Treacherous Trudy myself,
but I'll take it.
What brings you to my town?
I heard Rufus Buck was back.
News travels fast.
I have an offer he might wanna hear about.
Well, any offer you got,
you can make it to me.
I don't do business with the help.
Give me that shit.
Lead the way, Treacherous Trudy.
♫  Monday's child is ever smiling  ♫
♫  Tuesday's child will play inside  ♫
♫  Wednesday comes with a gun  ♫
♫  Thursday's tears have just begun  ♫
♫  Friday's ships are filled with crying  ♫
♫  Monday seems so far away now  ♫
♫  Tuesday was not bad at all  ♫
♫  Wednesday came with a flame  ♫
♫  Thursday never be the same  ♫
♫  Friday's ships are not returning  ♫
♫  Monday's child is torn asunder  ♫
♫  Tuesday's child is thrown in chains  ♫
♫  Wednesday's child used to smile  ♫
♫  Thursday's tears are now a Nile  ♫
♫  Friday's child is ever burning  ♫
Speak your piece.
I assume you know who I am.
I assume you know who I used to run with.
Those days are over for me anyhow,
but I didn't get to be
Stagecoach Mary Fields
without having my ears to the ground
and my ears tell me you just lost
25 thou that was coming your way.
I hope your proposal
rivals your nerve...
Allow me the latitude of completion.
My saloon in Douglas is boomin'.
Bought me another one in the Elks,
and I got a restaurant in Cascade too.
For the sum of all that,
I could take this one off your hands.
The mere mention of my name
brings forth good business
to any establishment attached, whereas,
with all due respect,
but the name Rufus Buck instils fear.
We know who you are.
You walkin' into my town
with that proposal is risky.
The kind of risk a woman such as yourself
wouldn't tie herself to
unless there was
a whole lot more at stake.
See, I don't believe in coincidence,
like you just gonna walk in here
right after the Crimson Hoods
get ambushed with my money.
What are you thinking?
Oops.
You must have forgot
whose name is on the door.
Another round.
We havin' a party, y'all. Come on.
All right, Mary.
All right.
So you still sayin'
you don't know nothin' about that money
and you done come here alone?
That's right.
You done rode all the way over here
to get yourself killed.
And for what?
For love?
Love is the only thing worth dying for.
But you wouldn't know anything about that.
You know,
I had a sister named Mary.
She was pretty, strong-willed, like you.
She died of polio when I was 11.
Always was in pain,
but she'd never let me see her cry.
Mmm.
There's this girl called Hope lived by us.
Big fat kid,
always picking on the smaller kids.
Obviously out of jealousy.
But she ain't never fuck with me though.
She hated Mary with a passion,
always teasing her
about how thin and frail she was.
Then one day,
Hope walkin' by our house,
apple in one hand, blade in the other.
She decided to throw the apple
across the street at Mary,
and it hit my sister in the head
and knocked her out of balance.
She fell down the steps.
Broke her ankle.
And now that...
that was the first and only time
I physically seen my sister cry.
And there was Hope standing there
laughin' her ugly fuckin' face off.
My daddy...
he got home,
he took off his belt, and he beat me
for not protecting my sister.
He lashed me
until my whole body went numb.
Then
he went to Hope house
to do the same thing to her.
When he got there, he saw her whole family
standin' on the side of the house,
all of 'em screamin' and cryin',
and there was Hope...
lyin' on the floor in a pool of blood.
Somebody had slit her throat.
Killed her with her own knife.
Daddy was speechless.
He ain't said a word to me
when he came home.
The next day,
he sent me to live with my grandparents.
And then the next time I seen my sister,
she was laying in a coffin.
Disease had killed her.
I'm sorry your sister had to suffer.
I admire her bravery.
But you get no words from me.
You know,
I actually admire your bravery.
But I'm afraid the outcome
is still the outcome.
Hope
must die.
But not yet.
Leave her out here in the street
so everybody can see her.
No one come to collect her 'fore sunup,
put a bullet in her head.
Yes, ma'am.
Looks like we don't
have to wait that long.
Whoever die first, right?
- Whoever die first.
- Mmm-hmm.
Get her up.
"Whoever die first"?
Now, what kind of dumbass saying is that?
You two trying to get shot out here?
Nat Love. How predictable.
You predict my friend Bill Pickett
aiming at your bowler cap?
You'll be dead
before your boys get their aim.
And you die right after.
But your boss won't see
one red cent of that money.
My boss?
Where is he?
Where is who?
Marshal.
I'm speakin' English, yeah?
- Sound like English to me.
- Mmm-hmm.
Where's Rufus Buck?
Oh.
Ooh-hoo.
Bass.
Trudy.
If I'd known you were switchin' sides,
I'da asked you to come join us.
You here for your damsel in distress?
You don't look hard of hearing.
So I'ma ask you again.
Where's Rufus Buck?
Well, clearly, you don't know me.
Tell your men to go,
but you stay,
and maybe your damsel
will live a little longer.
Marshal.
Oh.
You're pretty though.
- Ah, take her ass back in there.
- Yes, ma'am.
Gonna get me a drink.
Hey.
That the quick draw
I hear tell about, Cherokee Bill?
I hear you so fast
that your opponents ain't got time to draw
before you put two in they back.
No, that ain't me.
I'm the Cherokee Bill that shoots men
in the mouth that talk too much.
I'll make it easy for you, then.
You draw first.
That what you think this is?
"Who the quickest draw in the West?"
All comes down
to who fast and who ain't, right?
No, it all comes down
to who's alive and who's dead.
Trudy, I'm gonna get me
something to drink.
Good night.
Hey, hey, drink, my ass, man.
- I practiced that standoff all night.
- Jim.
- You're not about to walk away.
- Get out of here.
- No, nobody...
- Get out of here, Jim.
- That chicken...
- It ain't the time.
Okay. Okay.
March, boy.
- I said march!
- March.
Hup, two, three, four.
That's enough.
They beat you bad?
I'ma kill 'em all.
You familiar with Napoleon?
He said, "I am driven towards an end
that I do not know."
"As I reach it,
as I shall become unnecessary,
an atom shall suffice to shatter me."
"Until then, all forces of humankind
can do nothing to stop me."
That's a man who knew exactly who he was.
Most importantly,
he knew that
his time would come to an end.
Cut him down.
You know why...
I gave you that scar?
So I'd remember you.
No.
No, I gave you that scar so I can know
your face when you come back to me.
Nat Love,
the outlaw who robs outlaws,
the angel of death who hunts down those
who trespass against him with no mercy.
I know who you are.
And I see the line that you won't cross.
See, I know what's on the other side.
Apologize for the beating.
It was more of an indication
for what Ms. Fields might see
if we fail to come to terms.
What terms?
You will return the money
you stole from me by Friday noon.
Not a moment later.
And you will add $10,000 on top of that.
We'll call that interest.
Somethin' funny?
Ooh, shit, how...
how you reckon I'ma get that?
You're gonna rob a bank.
Nat Love is gonna rob a bank.
In the meantime, here's a little token
of my appreciation in advance.
Go ahead, open it.
I expect my money on Friday.
All of it.
You know I can't let you do that.
If that money ain't in Rufus' hands
in three days, Mary'll die.
What bank
we talking about anyway?
Maysville.
Maysville?
That's a white town.
Yeah, which is why
they gonna have $10,000 in their bank.
It's crazy.
My emotions
are all types of confused.
I mean, Pickett, I agree. That's crazy.
But, Nat, I also agree with you
telling the marshal
that we gonna do that shit anyways.
That's some true outlaw shit.
- We outlaws, ain't we?
- Ain't no "we," Jim.
Not after that shit you pulled in town
nearly got us all killed.
I had that.
Fetch that money
you took from the Crimson Hoods.
Pickett, kid, you comin' with me.
If Rufus Buck want that bank took,
why don't he send his own men?
This way he clean, see?
I gotta go in barefaced as day,
a freshly minted bank robber, face up
on wanted posters all over the territory.
They'll be on you like flies on shit
before you open the door.
Yep.
I said I had to be recognized.
Go ahead.
Hell no.
For Mary.
Whoo! Hoo!
Close shave.
Close fucking shave!
I thought I was
falling for a fella for a little bit.
That's why I didn't say nothing.
Well, I ain't the only one. I can't...
I can't... It wasn't just me.
It wasn't just me.
It was just you, Jim.
♫  Follow, follow
People they go they follow  ♫
♫  People they know they copy
Go all up in my grotto  ♫
♫  They see me like a genie
Try to keep me in a bottle  ♫
♫  Petty, petty people
Keep them incommunicado  ♫
♫  They tie you up with strings
They play niggas like pizzicato  ♫
Giddup now.
Allow me.
What's your real name?
Cuffee my real name.
Name I was born with?
Cathay Williams.
You walk worse than you ride, Cathay.
Mr. Love, my momma always told me
to respect my elders,
so I'm not gonna say what I'm thinking.
That's all right. I can read your mind.
Then I'm sorry you had to hear that.
Go ahead.
Go ahead, honey.
Yes?
I'd like to make a withdrawal.
Ooh.
What...
You have to have an account, ma'am.
And, well, I'd recommend a bank
in Jericho or maybe Redwood for that.
Oh.
I'm not talking about
that kinda withdrawal.
I'm talk...
I'm talking about...
talking about that kind.
Hey, blue eyes.
You scared.
Your hand is shaking. You'll miss.
I won't.
Exhale.
Attaboy.
I ain't like my partner.
He don't wanna shoot nobody,
but all of a sudden, I'm of a mind to.
Now open the fuckin' gate.
Think I'm funny now?
What you lookin' at?
Get all the customers over there.
- Get 'em over there!
- Okay, okay.
- Everyone, please, this way quickly.
- You too. Move!
Times have changed, ain't they?
They say robbing banks is hard work.
That's a lie. Robbing banks is easy.
The hard part is doing it without killing.
So, what'll it be...
Mr. Manager?
Good man.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Giddyap. Go.
Come on, come on.
- Pleasure banking with you.
- Okay, sir.
Nat Love.
Don't even look like much.
Ain't what it look like.
It's what it can buy you.
Rufus won't let Mary go
once he gets that money.
Yeah, I know it.
He'll kill her,
let me go, so's I carry that hurt with me.
So what, we just went through
all that trouble for nothin'?
Now we got something he want.
And that's it?
Gonna have to be.
You can be all hasty
and shoot me now if you want,
or you can wait to see
what I brought with me first.
Ooh.
Rufus got stashes like this
all across these hills.
Enough for a small army.
Don't nobody take what I got coming to me.
Not even the Devil himself.
Rufus Buck is a man.
Y'all best reconcile yourselves
with that fact.
Man or devil,
this gonna be
Buck's last day amongst the living.
♫  Upon my return  ♫
♫  See a changed soul  ♫
♫  That road was far
That road was far  ♫
♫  And way too long
And way too long  ♫
♫  They'll run from me
They'll run from me  ♫
♫  As they ran from you
As they ran from you  ♫
♫  That fear in me
That fear in me  ♫
♫  Is in a distant view  ♫
♫  Is  ♫
♫  In a distant  ♫
♫  View  ♫
Whoa there, whoa there. Whoa.
Afternoon.
I would ask you to run
go fetch your superior,
but that'd be like asking you
to run go fetch your daddy.
It could be anybody, right?
Hmm.
You know,
I'm willing to bet my right arm
I've got a higher body count than yours.
That'd be a bad bet, son.
I fancy that song or whatever it was
you was whistling there.
Go, Jerry. Go.
That our money?
Uh...
Walk with me.
Hey, just... just walk with me.
- Keep an eye on this, Angel.
- Mmm-hmm.
You know they call your boss
the Devil hisself?
Even the Devil needed money, right?
So being as how we are
in possession of that money...
let me dictate the terms of engagement.
What the fuck was that?
What the fuck was that, old man?
Is that the right arm or the left?
Oh man.
Well, now there's us...
and there's y'all.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You get a hold of your feisty buddy here.
You got a little rowdy rascal.
- Mary.
- Yeah, we'll get to that.
- We gonna count this first.
- Now, Cherokee.
Or your boss gonna be
one quick draw and $35,000 short.
All right.
Unhitch this horse so's Mary can ride out.
- You always move so slow?
- You always talk so much?
Really?
In the back?
What you think, Beckwourth?
Nah, he wouldn't do that
'cause then I would have to put
a bullet in his cranium.
And we'll never know
who the fastest really is now, will we?
I gotta hand it to you, boy.
You do know how to make a grand entrance.
Shit, I didn't even rehearse that one.
You know, quick draw,
Nat Love is a dead man walking.
But you don't have to be.
Why don't you get on your horse,
get your shit,
and go back to
whatever it is you call home?
You know that's impossible.
Count down from five?
Five...
Four...
Three...
Why do they always have to count so slow?
Jim!
Blow that bitch, Bill!
♫  Do unto others  ♫
♫  As you will have them do  ♫
Kill her.
♫  Oh, that reaper, he gonna win  ♫
♫  All them people that live in sin  ♫
♫  Give that lady a ring of fire  ♫
♫  You're dead in your blood  ♫
♫  That's yo woman
Ain't no better love  ♫
♫  All them people that live in sin  ♫
Mary!
Push!
♫  There dat coffin you gonna lie, so  ♫
Trudy's mine.
♫  Dead in your blood  ♫
♫  That's yo woman
Ain't no better love  ♫
We gonna play for you
our first tune tonight.
And the first tune is called...
O l'oun t'awa se n'yara. Je k'abere
Which means,
"Let's start what we have come
into the room to do."
Let's go.
♫  One, two, three!  ♫
Son of a bitch!
Exhale, motherfucker.
Come on.
- Where'd they get you?
- Shoulder. Get down!
Matches.
You wanna smoke now?
Matches, Bass.
Okay.
Jump, motherfuckers.
Fuck it.
I always knew it was you
who gave me up.
God knew my heart.
Goodbye, old friend.
Rufus, I didn't have a choice...
I told that kid.
Them damn tricks...
Sorry, ladies.
- You all right, Cuffee?
- Just need to reload.
You look hurt, Mr. Pickett.
Ain't nothing but a flesh wound.
Maggie ain't ready for me today.
Huh?
What the fuck?
I'll be damned.
Pickett!
Now, why you got
that look on your face?
No. No, no, no, brother, no, no, no.
Stop that. Don't do that.
You had a choice.
You always got a choice.
Being scared will only
give you bad karma in the afterlife.
He didn't even have a chance,
you son of a bitch!
You gonna shoot me in the back too?
Or cheat the count?
♫  I lost my shadow in violent sin  ♫
♫  Never knew the search would be within  ♫
Beckwourth was faster.
♫  Drew a picture of my only desire  ♫
♫  Take me back to Blackskin Mile  ♫
♫  I thought my karma would be my fate  ♫
♫  Never saw the sun
Until it was too late  ♫
♫  And, oh  ♫
♫  Drew my loneliness
Chasing every last high  ♫
♫  Take me back to Blackskin Mile  ♫
♫  I never met a madman's soul  ♫
♫  That I didn't see reflections
Of that which I own  ♫
♫  But I know
There's something better outside  ♫
♫  So won't you
Take me back to Blackskin Mile?  ♫
Look after my friend.
Nat.
Don't miss.
Pick up your guns.
I know what it is now.
It's the eyes.
Pick 'em up, I said.
Your father,
he was a good man?
He was.
And my mother was a good woman
before you cut 'em down.
Seems we had a different upbringing.
I don't care how you was raised.
Now pick up your guns and turn around.
I used to watch my father
beat my mother to a pulp
if she overcooked his food.
He cut her up real good
if she undercooked it too.
One day, I decided to intervene,
and he turned his wrath on me.
My father was not a good man.
Not a good man. He was an outlaw.
Robbin' banks...
He liked to drink.
My mother took a bottle
and cut him to protect me.
He lashed back at her,
and just like that, she was gone.
Then, like the coward he is,
he took everything we had and left,
leaving me with my...
my mother.
I was ten years old, you know...
about the same age you was...
when I gave you that scar.
I had to fend for myself,
but I became who I am,
just like you.
As I did, all I could ever think about is
wanting my father to pay for what he did.
I searched for him for years and years,
and I could never find him.
It's like he disappeared
off the face of the earth.
I ain't stop though. I kept looking...
until I did find him.
One day...
lo and behold,
there he was,
my father,
a new man.
He was clean now.
Sober.
Man of God.
Had a church.
He had a pretty little wife.
And he had a son,
about the age of ten years old,
whose eyes blazed like mine.
You're lyin'.
You're lyin'!
Killing our father was retribution, but...
My father!
My mother!
But it weren't enough.
Letting you live,
that was the true revenge.
Every sin you made, every bank you robbed,
everybody you killed.
I mean, look at you.
You everything he tried to run away from.
Buck.
Changed his name to "Love."
You a Buck.
You lyin'.
Just like me.
Just like him.
But you better.
You gonna surpass even me because...
I couldn't kill my brother.
Yet here you are about to kill yours.
It's time to take your revenge,
Nathaniel Buck.
Go on.
- Nathaniel Buck.
- No.
Take your revenge.
Nathaniel Buck.
Take your goddamn revenge!
You a Buck.
Nathaniel Buck.
Nathaniel...
♫  And upon my return  ♫
♫  You'll see a changed soul  ♫
♫  The road  ♫
♫  Was far too long  ♫
Is the Devil dead?
I don't know.
♫  They'll run from me  ♫
♫  As they ran from you  ♫
♫  The fear in me  ♫
♫  Is in a distant view  ♫
♫  And there ain't no turning around  ♫
All right, fellas.
You sure the law gonna believe he's dead?
I'm the law, Ms. Mary.
If I say a man dead, he dead.
And you?
You sure this what you want?
I always kinda wanted to be
a deputy, sheriff, marshal person.
♫  Hold up your lighter and come  ♫
♫  Flame inna de air, fire fi bun  ♫
♫  Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry  ♫
♫  Tell them
Say my love will never die  ♫
What you lookin' at?
We got work to do, Mr. Love.
Hup.
Let's go.
♫  And when we get there, we shall sing  ♫
♫  The harder they fall  ♫
♫  Across the heaven
Love shall ring, ring, ring...  ♫
All right.
♫  Where shall we walk?
Where shall we run and run?  ♫
Where shall we run?  ♫
♫  Over the mountain to the sun  ♫
♫  On to the sun  ♫
♫  And when we get there, we shall sing  ♫
♫  And we shall sing  ♫
♫  Across the heaven
Love will ring, ring, ring, ring  ♫
♫  Hold up your lighter and come  ♫
♫  Flame inna de air, fire fi bun  ♫
♫  Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry  ♫
♫  Tell 'em
Say my love will never die  ♫
♫  Where do we go?  ♫
♫  A long and winding road  ♫
♫  The louder they roar  ♫
♫  The harder that they fall  ♫
♫  See fi de man with him bible and gun
See him deh  ♫
♫  Badman no scarper nah run  ♫
♫  See fi de woman afraid of no man
See she deh  ♫
♫  Bad gyal no scarper nah run
Pam pam  ♫
♫  Lick a shot
And every man wave your hand  ♫
♫  Pam pam
All of de woman jussa rise and stand  ♫
♫  Oh gosh
Bandolero dem a watch when we walk  ♫
♫  Bad gyal no take bak no talk
When I say  ♫
♫  Hold up your lighter and come  ♫
♫  Flame inna de air, fire fi bun  ♫
♫  Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry  ♫
♫  Tell 'em
Say my love will never die  ♫
♫  Where do we go?  ♫
♫  A long and winding road  ♫
♫  The louder they roar  ♫
♫  The harder that they fall  ♫
♫  Fire fi bun
Mister Man we have no time to play  ♫
♫  You love a woman
Tell her night and day  ♫
♫  Send dem come
Jah know me tell you right away  ♫
♫  Me love you like me love me waistline  ♫
♫  Dress pretty pretty
Still me a walk nitty gritty  ♫
♫  Round up de woman committee
And ride fi him city  ♫
♫  Two of we a free like bird
So better they listen my word  ♫
♫  When I say
Hold up your lighter and come  ♫
♫  Flame inna de air, fire fi bun  ♫
♫  Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry  ♫
♫  Tell 'em say my love will never die  ♫
♫  Where do we go?  ♫
♫  A long and winding road  ♫
♫  The louder they roar  ♫
♫  The harder that they fall  ♫
♫  Better we fall  ♫
♫  Our time is borrowed  ♫
♫  Live like it's our last day  ♫
♫  There is no tomorrow  ♫
♫  We'll be reborn  ♫
♫  In a beautiful morning  ♫
♫  Blowing like tumbleweed  ♫
♫  Night come like thief  ♫
♫  Till rooster crow  ♫
♫  I know, I know we'll...  ♫
♫  Hold up your lighter and come  ♫
♫  Flame inna de air, fire fi bun  ♫
♫  Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry  ♫
♫  Tell 'em
Say my love will never die  ♫
♫  Where do we go?  ♫
♫  A long and winding road  ♫
♫  The louder they roar  ♫
♫  The harder that they fall  ♫
♫  Every day we go harder  ♫
♫  For the night, we live faster  ♫
♫  When the rain come down harder  ♫
♫  Light a flame, we go faster  ♫
♫  For the pain will try test we  ♫
♫  No Wahala can best we  ♫
♫  Better know we don't lazy  ♫
♫  Better know we go crazy  ♫
♫  Every day we go harder  ♫
♫  For the night, we live faster  ♫
♫  When the rain come down harder  ♫
♫  Light a flame, we go faster  ♫
♫  For the pain will try test we  ♫
♫  No Wahala can best we  ♫
♫  Better know we don't lazy  ♫
♫  Better know we go crazy  ♫
♫  Every day we go hard  ♫
♫  For the night, we live fast  ♫
♫  When the rain come down hard  ♫
♫  Light a flame, we go fast  ♫
♫  Go bring dem, come we go  ♫
♫  Go louder, silence no  ♫
♫  Come fire, water go  ♫
♫  Sing higher, cry no mo'  ♫
♫  Nobody came for we
We tired, oh  ♫
♫  Fire the flame they see
We stronger, oh  ♫
♫  Every day we go harder  ♫
♫  For the night, we live faster  ♫
♫  When the rain come down harder  ♫
♫  Light a flame, we go faster  ♫
♫  For the pain will try test we  ♫
♫  No Wahala can best we  ♫
♫  Better know we don't lazy  ♫
♫  Better know we go crazy  ♫
♫  Every day we go harder  ♫
♫  For the night, we live faster  ♫
♫  When the rain come down harder  ♫
♫  Light a flame, we go faster  ♫
♫  For the pain will try test we  ♫
♫  No Wahala can best we  ♫
♫  Better know we don't lazy  ♫
♫  Better know we go crazy  ♫
♫  For the pain will try test we  ♫
♫  No Wahala can best we  ♫
♫  Better know we don't lazy  ♫
♫  Better know we go crazy  ♫
♫  And upon my return  ♫
♫  You'll see a changed soul  ♫
♫  The road was far too long  ♫
♫  They'll run from me  ♫
♫  As they ran from you  ♫
♫  The fear in me  ♫
♫  Is in a distant view  ♫
♫  And there ain't no turning around  ♫
♫  Here I go, no mercy for the sinner  ♫
♫  Don't you ever turn around  ♫
♫  Here I go  ♫
♫  It hurts within the winter  ♫
♫  Never, ever make a sound  ♫
♫  Don't you ever  ♫
♫  Never, ever  ♫
♫  Make a sound  ♫
♫  And upon my return  ♫
♫  You'll see a changed soul  ♫
♫  The road was far too long  ♫
♫  They'll run from me  ♫
♫  As they ran from you  ♫
♫  The fear in me  ♫
♫  Is in a distant view  ♫
♫  And there ain't no turning around  ♫
♫  No, there ain't...  ♫